[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Nastia, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Nastia", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "And these are all from Beijing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "these", "are", "all", "from", "Beijing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beijing"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "They're pretty cool, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "pretty", "cool", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "What does it feel like to actually own Olympic gold medals?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "feel", "like", "to", "actually", "own", "Olympic", "gold", "medals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "It's kind of surreal, because you know, this is something that you've been dreaming about for your whole entire life and ever since I knew like what the word Olympics meant, I always knew that I wanted to win a gold medal at the Olympic Games.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "kind", "of", "surreal", ",", "because", "you", "know", ",", "this", "is", "something", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "dreaming", "about", "for", "your", "whole", "entire", "life", "and", "ever", "since", "I", "knew", "like", "what", "the", "word", "Olympics", "meant", ",", "I", "always", "knew", "that", "I", "wanted", "to", "win", "a", "gold", "medal", "at", "the", "Olympic", "Games", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "And both competed for the Soviet Union, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "both", "competed", "for", "the", "Soviet", "Union", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Soviet Union"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Why are you not speaking like this, representing Russia?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "not", "speaking", "like", "this", ",", "representing", "Russia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, we moved to the United States when I was 2 1/2 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "moved", "to", "the", "United", "States", "when", "I", "was", "2", "1/2", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Where did you start in America?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "start", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "New Orleans.", "answer_tokens": ["New", "Orleans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "I do?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Would you go back to Russia?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "back", "to", "Russia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "We do.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Russia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "And how does your grandmother feel about you representing America?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "does", "your", "grandmother", "feel", "about", "you", "representing", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "I think they're OK with it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'re", "OK", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "How did they feel when you won the gold?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "they", "feel", "when", "you", "won", "the", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, my mom wasn't there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "mom", "was", "n't", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "She actually went to like some Chinese temple and you know, I had to call her as soon as I knew that I won, but she turned her phone on silent so nobody would break the news to her.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "actually", "went", "to", "like", "some", "Chinese", "temple", "and", "you", "know", ",", "I", "had", "to", "call", "her", "as", "soon", "as", "I", "knew", "that", "I", "won", ",", "but", "she", "turned", "her", "phone", "on", "silent", "so", "nobody", "would", "break", "the", "news", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "But America's been very good to you and your family, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "America", "'s", "been", "very", "good", "to", "you", "and", "your", "family", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "It definitely has and I think it's given us so many amazing opportunities.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "definitely", "has", "and", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "given", "us", "so", "many", "amazing", "opportunities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "So do you still -- you consider yourself really American or both?", "question_tokens": ["So", "do", "you", "still", "--", "you", "consider", "yourself", "really", "American", "or", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "You know, it's hard to answer that question.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "answer", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "What do you want me to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "me", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Whatever -- I wouldn't understand you anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Whatever", "--", "I", "would", "n't", "understand", "you", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Very sexy language, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "sexy", "language", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "You said you weren't going to be competing, and then you became the comeback kid at the grand old age of -- how old are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "said", "you", "were", "n't", "going", "to", "be", "competing", ",", "and", "then", "you", "became", "the", "comeback", "kid", "at", "the", "grand", "old", "age", "of", "--", "how", "old", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Twenty-two.", "answer_tokens": ["Twenty-two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What changed your mind?", "question_tokens": ["What", "changed", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "You know, there's something about the sport of gymnastics in the Olympic Games.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "there", "'s", "something", "about", "the", "sport", "of", "gymnastics", "in", "the", "Olympic", "Games", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Do you think you can win gold?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "can", "win", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Would you like to continue in some other form in gymnastics?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "continue", "in", "some", "other", "form", "in", "gymnastics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I was thinking I would retire until my dad, who coaches me still, said maybe you should compete at another world championships after and do another year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "thinking", "I", "would", "retire", "until", "my", "dad", ",", "who", "coaches", "me", "still", ",", "said", "maybe", "you", "should", "compete", "at", "another", "world", "championships", "after", "and", "do", "another", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "What do you think it takes to be a champion, to be an Olympic champion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "it", "takes", "to", "be", "a", "champion", ",", "to", "be", "an", "Olympic", "champion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I think it obviously it takes a lot of hard work.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "obviously", "it", "takes", "a", "lot", "of", "hard", "work", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "You trained Christmas Day?", "question_tokens": ["You", "trained", "Christmas", "Day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Who are your great role models?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "your", "great", "role", "models", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "You know, it sounds so --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "sounds", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "-- just casually on television, what you can say to try and get them to take a different path?", "question_tokens": ["--", "just", "casually", "on", "television", ",", "what", "you", "can", "say", "to", "try", "and", "get", "them", "to", "take", "a", "different", "path", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I think it's really important to understand that, you know, you can achieve anything that you set your mind to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "really", "important", "to", "understand", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "can", "achieve", "anything", "that", "you", "set", "your", "mind", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I guess, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "ORGAN: Is that how you see yourself?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "that", "how", "you", "see", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I see myself as a normal 19-year-old kid.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "see", "myself", "as", "a", "normal", "19-year-old", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Who just happens to be a gold medal contending power ball?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "just", "happens", "to", "be", "a", "gold", "medal", "contending", "power", "ball", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Yes, I guess.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What was it like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Growing up in the Bronx, especially as a gymnast, it's not easy.", "answer_tokens": ["Growing", "up", "in", "the", "Bronx", ",", "especially", "as", "a", "gymnast", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "It wasn't masculine enough for them?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "n't", "masculine", "enough", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Why gymnastics?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "gymnastics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I love gymnast -- I -- I took gymnastics because it's one of the most challenging sports in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "gymnast", "--", "I", "--", "I", "took", "gymnastics", "because", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "most", "challenging", "sports", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "-- this was going to be you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "this", "was", "going", "to", "be", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I just felt it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "felt", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Westchester"]}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "I mean, going from one place to somewhere completely different?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "going", "from", "one", "place", "to", "somewhere", "completely", "different", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Yes, I'm glad I got to train in Westchester.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "glad", "I", "got", "to", "train", "in", "Westchester", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What are the good parts of you that you think come from being a Bronx guy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "good", "parts", "of", "you", "that", "you", "think", "come", "from", "being", "a", "Bronx", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I mean, well, look at my parents.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "well", ",", "look", "at", "my", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "And I mean with people like that in the Bronx, you can't be that bad, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "mean", "with", "people", "like", "that", "in", "the", "Bronx", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "be", "that", "bad", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Did you get into fights with the kids in the Bronx?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "into", "fights", "with", "the", "kids", "in", "the", "Bronx", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Does everybody have to fight, for a young man growing up in the Bronx?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "everybody", "have", "to", "fight", ",", "for", "a", "young", "man", "growing", "up", "in", "the", "Bronx", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Knives, as well?", "question_tokens": ["Knives", ",", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "He was stabbed?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "stabbed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "No, thank God.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "thank", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "What did -- what did it teach you, the incident?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "--", "what", "did", "it", "teach", "you", ",", "the", "incident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "That life is unpredictable and you can't -- you can't let -- you can't hold onto that.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "life", "is", "unpredictable", "and", "you", "ca", "n't", "--", "you", "ca", "n't", "let", "--", "you", "ca", "n't", "hold", "onto", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Do you see, in the future, a life for them out of the Bronx?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", ",", "in", "the", "future", ",", "a", "life", "for", "them", "out", "of", "the", "Bronx", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "I mean because you're, what are you, 19?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "because", "you", "'re", ",", "what", "are", "you", ",", "19", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Nineteen.", "answer_tokens": ["Nineteen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "This is not a world that you're allowed to do, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "not", "a", "world", "that", "you", "'re", "allowed", "to", "do", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "It's -- it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "If you perform at your absolute best, what can you achieve in London?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "perform", "at", "your", "absolute", "best", ",", "what", "can", "you", "achieve", "in", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I think if I do my absolute best, I think -- I think I might have a chance of being on the medal stand and all around.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "if", "I", "do", "my", "absolute", "best", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "I", "might", "have", "a", "chance", "of", "being", "on", "the", "medal", "stand", "and", "all", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "And if you win a gold -- how is that going to make you feel, a boy from the Bronx winning an Olympic Gold Medal, standing on that podium, the American national anthem playing?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "win", "a", "gold", "--", "how", "is", "that", "going", "to", "make", "you", "feel", ",", "a", "boy", "from", "the", "Bronx", "winning", "an", "Olympic", "Gold", "Medal", ",", "standing", "on", "that", "podium", ",", "the", "American", "national", "anthem", "playing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "That would be a dream come true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "a", "dream", "come", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "It would be an emotional moment for you, huh?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "an", "emotional", "moment", "for", "you", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Yes, definitely an emotional moment for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "an", "emotional", "moment", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "And your parents?", "question_tokens": ["And", "your", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "And my family.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "my", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", ":", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "I am?", "question_tokens": ["I", "am", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "That's what -- that's what I'm hearing.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "--", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "hearing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Are you ready for the screaming women chasing you down the street?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ready", "for", "the", "screaming", "women", "chasing", "you", "down", "the", "street", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "And if you win the gold, can you imagine all those guys who teased you back in the Bronx, are you going to be thinking of their pictures, of their faces?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "win", "the", "gold", ",", "can", "you", "imagine", "all", "those", "guys", "who", "teased", "you", "back", "in", "the", "Bronx", ",", "are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "thinking", "of", "their", "pictures", ",", "of", "their", "faces", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "No, no, no, no, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Shoot up in your face and you stand there?", "question_tokens": ["Shoot", "up", "in", "your", "face", "and", "you", "stand", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "No, never.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "It will be a little bit, won't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "will", "be", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "wo", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Being an American?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "an", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Aly, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Aly", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "I'm very good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "You're 17 years old, but in gymnastics terms, I mean, you're quite old, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "17", "years", "old", ",", "but", "in", "gymnastics", "terms", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "quite", "old", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes, I'm definitely, I guess, considered old for gymnastics.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "definitely", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "considered", "old", "for", "gymnastics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "How you feeling?", "question_tokens": ["How", "you", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "I'm feeling very confident.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "feeling", "very", "confident", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "The amount of training you do for this kind of thing must be absurd, it's just relentless, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "amount", "of", "training", "you", "do", "for", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "must", "be", "absurd", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "relentless", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Seeing all your mates off down, I don't know where they go, the night clubs, having fun, listening to the music, going out, eating bad food, having donuts, do you miss any of that?", "question_tokens": ["Seeing", "all", "your", "mates", "off", "down", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "where", "they", "go", ",", "the", "night", "clubs", ",", "having", "fun", ",", "listening", "to", "the", "music", ",", "going", "out", ",", "eating", "bad", "food", ",", "having", "donuts", ",", "do", "you", "miss", "any", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "I mean, I used to miss it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "used", "to", "miss", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "You don't feel you're missing anything?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "feel", "you", "'re", "missing", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "No, I don't at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Is winning an Olympic gold for you the absolute number one dream?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "winning", "an", "Olympic", "gold", "for", "you", "the", "absolute", "number", "one", "dream", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "AISMAN: Yes, definitely, winning the Olympic gold, it just gives me chills thinking about it, and I've been dreaming about that ever since I was a little girl.", "answer_tokens": ["AISMAN", ":", "Yes", ",", "definitely", ",", "winning", "the", "Olympic", "gold", ",", "it", "just", "gives", "me", "chills", "thinking", "about", "it", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "been", "dreaming", "about", "that", "ever", "since", "I", "was", "a", "little", "girl", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Is it literally all seven hours a day you're thinking about gold medals, the podium, the American anthem?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "literally", "all", "seven", "hours", "a", "day", "you", "'re", "thinking", "about", "gold", "medals", ",", "the", "podium", ",", "the", "American", "anthem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Yes, definitely, especially in the car ride to and from gym I find myself thinking out a lot, just visualizing what the Olympics would be like and just having such great role models.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", ",", "especially", "in", "the", "car", "ride", "to", "and", "from", "gym", "I", "find", "myself", "thinking", "out", "a", "lot", ",", "just", "visualizing", "what", "the", "Olympics", "would", "be", "like", "and", "just", "having", "such", "great", "role", "models", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Are you allowed to have boyfriends?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "allowed", "to", "have", "boyfriends", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I mean, right now I'm not, I don't have a boyfriend, but maybe after the summer I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "right", "now", "I", "'m", "not", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "boyfriend", ",", "but", "maybe", "after", "the", "summer", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "So that's banned before the Olympics?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "'s", "banned", "before", "the", "Olympics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Is he like your boyfriend?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "like", "your", "boyfriend", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "No, he's not like my boyfriend, but he's a very nice guy and he's one of my good friends.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "like", "my", "boyfriend", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "a", "very", "nice", "guy", "and", "he", "'s", "one", "of", "my", "good", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "So that's important, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "'s", "important", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Yes, that's very important to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "very", "important", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Because you started all this when you went to a mommy and me class when you were 3 years old, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "started", "all", "this", "when", "you", "went", "to", "a", "mommy", "and", "me", "class", "when", "you", "were", "3", "years", "old", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Are you a good loser?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "good", "loser", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "I do not like to lose at all, but it motivates me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "not", "like", "to", "lose", "at", "all", ",", "but", "it", "motivates", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "What does it mean to you to be an American in the Olympics?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", "to", "be", "an", "American", "in", "the", "Olympics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "It means everything to me just to be able to represent the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "means", "everything", "to", "me", "just", "to", "be", "able", "to", "represent", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]